Jan Karon papers MSS 16077
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
Jan Karon papers
1918-2016, bulk 1964-2016
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
Karon, Jan (Janice), 1937-
MSS 16077
66 Cubic Feet The Jan Karon papers consist of 120 legal Hollinger boxes, 3 oversize boxes, 17 oversize folders, 17 audio cassettes, 26 videocassettes, 46 disks, and 2 hard drives.
Conditions Governing Access
There are no access restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Jan Karon papers were given to the University of Virginia Library on October 2, 2014, by Jan Karon.
Arrangement
The Jan Karon papers are organized into eight series. Series I consists of manuscripts and book related material, including illustrations, book jackets and covers, reviews, editorial files, radio plays, stage plays, page proofs, and galleys (Boxes 1-26 and Oversize boxes 1, 3). Series II consists of reader mail from fans (Boxes 27-43).
Series III contains the professional correspondence and papers of Jan Karon concerning the publication of her books, including files with publishers, arrangements and publicity for public appearances, press clippings, and interviews (Boxes 44-59, oversize folder 17 and oversize boxes 1 and 3).
Series IV consists of personal and family papers and is further separated into two subseries,subseries A: personal and family correspondence (Boxes 59-83), including greeting cards and invitations, with frequent correspondents having an individual folder and subseries B: personal papers of Jan Karon, including calendar diaries, journals, personal notes, and related material (Boxes 84-86 and Oversize box 3).
Series V includes materials relating to her advertising career, including the North Carolina tourism campaign (Boxes 87-90 and Oversize box 1).
Series VI contains topical files, including organizations, newsletters, travel files, Mitford general files, and research files Boxes 90-100).
Series VII consists of records about the purchase and restoration of her historic home "Esmont" in Ablemarle County, Virginia, including architectural drawings in Subseries A (Oversize folders 1-16 and Oversize boxes 2-3) and papers and photographs in Subseries B (Boxes 101-113).
Series VIII comprises the last series and consists of artifacts, miscellany, audiovisual and born-digital material (Boxes 114-120). This series is arranged in four subseries: Subseries A: Artifacts, chiefly concerning the Second International Mitford Homecoming; Subseries B: Albums and Volumes;Subseries C: Books Influential in the Life of Jan Karon; and Subseries D: Audiovisual and Born Digital Material.
Biographical / Historical
Jan Karon is an American novelist who writes for both adults and young readers. She is the author of the "New York Times" bestselling Mitford novels, featuring Father Timothy Kavanagh, an Episcopal priest, and the fictional village of Mitford. (Wikipedia)
Jan Karon was born on March 14, 1937 in Lenoir, North Carolina, to Robert Cecil Wilson (1914-1977) and Wanda Lee Wilson (1921- ) and was named Janice Meredith after the title of a popular novel. She and her younger sister, Brenda, lived as children with her grandparents, Monroe Ivy Cloer and Fannie Bush Cloer, on their farm outside Hudson, North Carolina. Both sisters later moved to Charlotte, North Carolina to join their mother who had married Toby Setzer, the owner of a hosiery knitting business.
At fourteen, Karon married Robert Bryan Freeland (1932-1995) in Charlotte and had one daughter, Candace Rae Freeland, in 1952. Her advertising career began at the age of eighteen, at Walter J. Klein Company, one of the first advertising agencies in the region.
Karon’s marriage to Robert Freeland ended in divorce and in her early twenties, Karon married a Duke Power chemist, Bill Orth, and became active in the Charlotte Little Theater, the Mint Museum Drama Guild, and in local social and political issues. She was one of four white women who marched in an early civil rights protest, led by the Reverend Sydney Freeman, along Charlotte’s North Tyron Street.
During the late sixties, she and Orth divorced. Karon then married Arthur Karon, a clothing salesman who moved the family to Berkeley, California, where they lived for three years.
After their marriage ended, Karon returned to Charlotte, North Carolina, and begun working again in advertising. Her dismissal from a Charlotte TV production company in 1982 precipitated what she called the ‘proverbial dark night of the soul.’ Karon returned to the faith taught her as a child by her grandmother. She began attending Charlotte’s interdenominational Calvary Church, and worked as a free-lance copywriter until her move to Raleigh, North Carolina, in 1983, where she joined McKinney and Silver, an internationally renowned advertising firm.
She became an award- winning creative vice-president at McKinney, working on cruise line and airline accounts. There she won, with art director Michael Winslow, the coveted Steven E. Kelly Award, the print advertising equivalent of the Academy Award. Semi-finalists included British Airways, Harley-Davidson, and Waterford Crystal.
Her daughter, Candace Freeland, pursued photojournalism, winning numerous awards with the "Miami Herald", the "Charlotte Observer", and a stint in Central America for the "U.S. News and World Report".
In order to purse her dream of writing a novel, Karon left her advertising career and, at age fifty, bought a house in the small mountain town of Blowing Rock, North Carolina, where she supported her dream with freelance advertising work.
Soon, she approached the editor of "The Blowing Rocket" with a couple of chapters featuring an Episcopal priest named Tim Kavanagh, which he urged her to run in "The Blowing Rocket". The ensuing two years of writing the priest’s story for "The Blowing Rocket" resulted in her first novel, "At Home in Mitford", published in paper by a small publishing house in the Midwest. Twenty years after its initial release in paper, the novel appeared in its 85th printing, in a new, 20th anniversary hardcover edition, from Penguin-Random House, the world’s largest trade publisher.
The second and third Mitford novels, "A Light in the Window" and "These High Green Hills", were published by the same house, with limited marketing and distribution. Karon took the promotion of her books into her own hands, cold-selling them to bookstores and befriending bookstore owners. In Raleigh, bookseller Nancy Olson of Quail Ridge Books, was given a copy of "At Home in Mitford" by Mary Richardson, Karon’s Raleigh neighbor and friend. Olson admired the work and in 1996 introduced Karon to literary agent Liz Darhansoff. Darhansoff showed the Karon books to Carolyn Carlson at Penguin, and a long and fruitful relationship began. At this writing (2016), Karon has published twenty-two works of fiction and non-fiction, with sales estimated at more than 40 million, not including foreign sales in nineteen countries. Karon is currently published by G.P. Putnam’s Sons, an imprint of Penguin-Random House; her editor is Christine Pepe.
Jan Karon has won much recognition for her work. Among these are three nominations by the American Booksellers Association of "At Home in Mitford" for Best Book of the Year for three consecutive years (1996-1998) – a one-time-only occurrence in the Association’s history to date.
In 2013, "Somewhere Safe with Somebody Good", which spent seventeen weeks on the New York Times bestseller list, was given the Library of Virginia’s Best Fiction of the Year award. In 2015, Karon received The Library of Virginia’s Lifetime Achievement Award. And in 2016, "Come Rain or Come Shine" debuting at #1 on the "New York Times" list, was the recipient of the 2016 Christy Award. A further recognition is the designation of Jan Karon as a lay Canon for the Arts in the Episcopal Diocese of Quincy. For more information about honors and awards, see box 44 of this collection.
For more information about Jan Karon and her books, see the publicity – press files in boxes 55-56 of this collection, a long article in "The Charlotte Observer", August 14, 2005, her facebook page https://www.facebook.com/JanKaron/ and website http://www.mitfordbooks.com/, as well as her Wikipedia entry: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jan_Karon
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
There are two hard drives in this collection that are currently unavailable.
Appointments must be made in advance to use media formats such as LPs, audiotapes, videotapes, films, CDs, and DVDs held by Special Collections. In most cases, materials must be reformatted before they can be accessed, sometimes at the researcher's expense. Please use our online reference request form to ask for further information or to schedule access to audio-visual materials. Access cannot be guaranteed unless prior arrangements have been made.
Scope and Contents
The Jan Karon papers contain Mitford book typescripts and galleys; materials related to Ms. Karon's publishing career and her relationship with her agent and publisher; letters and fan mail from readers, arranged by month and year only; memorabilia; professional and personal correspondence; reviews and press publicity; research related to Karon's novels; files related to charitable organizations and boards; architectural drawings of Esmont Farm; files and journals related to the purchase, restoration, and running of historic Esmont Farm, Albemarle County, Virginia, by Karon; personal and family papers; files pertaining to Jan Karon’s advertising career, particularly the North Carolina tourism campaign for McKinney & Silver; photographs; artifacts; audiovisual material; and born-digital material, including disks and hard drives.
Mitford (N.C.: Imaginary place)--Fiction; Authors and publishers; Esmont (Albemarle County, Va.: Dwelling); Advertising; Novelists, American; Karon, Jan (Janice), 1937-; Read, Miss (Saint, Dora Jessie) -- correspondence; Setzer family -- correspondence; Bush, Barbara, 1925- -- correspondence; Viking Press -- correspondence; Freeland, Candace Rae, 1952- -- correspondence; Jordan, Daniel P. -- correspondence; Jordan, Lou (Jordan, Lewellyn Schmelzer) -- correspondence; Richardson, Mary Williams, 1914-2009 -- correspondence; Richardson, Jerry, 1936- -- correspondence; Hallmark Properties -- correspondence; Lion Publishing (Firm) -- correspondence; Penguin (Firm) -- correspondence; G.P. Putnam's Sons -- correspondence
- Book manuscripts and related material
  - "At Home in Mitford," uncorrected proof copy, spiral bound, published by Lion Publishing, 458 pages, signed by Jan Karon, [1994]; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "At Home in Mitford," uncorrected proof copy, published by Lion Publishing, Chapters 1-3, [1994]; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "At Home in Mitford," covers and book jacket art, [1994-1997]; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "At Home in Mitford," publicity and promotion, 1994, 2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical score for the theater adaptation of the novel by Jan Karon, music by Carl Johnson, and lyrics by Chana Wise, spiral bound, 2009 June 25; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical theater adaptation of the novel by Jan Karon; book by Cynthia Ferrell, music by Carl Johnson, and lyrics by Chana Wise, spiral bound, 2009 June 25; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical theater adaptation of the novel by Jan Karon; book by Cynthia Ferrell, music by Carl Johnson, and lyrics by Chana Wise, spiral bound, with comments by Jan Karon concerning the script, 2009 June 25-July 5; 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A staged reading of "At Home in Mitford," the musical based on the novel by Jan Karon, at the Academy for New Musical Theatre, including a program for the event, in a white binder, [2009] May 21; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," author’s notes and research, 2011-2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," editorial correspondence, publicity and reviews, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," interior design layouts and book jacket designs, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," typed manuscript with deletions noted and legal changes made concerning song lyrics, 2015; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," galley, 1st pass master (1 of 2 folders), 2015 May 15; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," galley, 1st pass master (2 of 2 folders), 2015 May 15; 1 folder(s) (Box 2-A, Folder 1)
  - "Come Rain or Come Shine," galley, 1st pass master, pages where corrections have been made by the author, 2015 June 1; 1 folder(s) (Box 2-A, Folder 2)
  - "A Common Life," cover art and illustrations, 2000-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 2-A, Folder 3)
  - "A Common Life," editorial correspondence and author’s notes, 1996-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 2-A, Folder 4)
  - "A Common Life," typed manuscript, setting copy with corrections and additions, 177 pages, [2000 June 29]; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "A Common Life," revised layouts, 2000 July 6; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "A Common Life," author’s rough pages, 2000 July 13; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "A Common Life," reviews and publicity, 2000-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "A Common Life," reviews and publicity, 2002-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "A Continual Feast," editorial correspondence, cover art, and advertising copy, 2004-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "A Continual Feast," typed manuscript with corrections and changes, author’s rough pages, [2004]-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "A Continual Feast," page proofs, author’s set, first pass, 2004 June; 1 folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Esther’s Gift," editorial correspondence, publicity, illustrations and book jacket proofs, 2001-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Esther’s Gift," typed manuscripts, layouts with black and white illustrations, and page proofs, 2001-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," audiobook, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," author's notes and copy, circa 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," brochures on Holly Springs, Mississippi, circa 2000-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," contacts and businesses in Holly Springs, Mississippi, circa 2002-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," correspondence with residents in Holly Springs, Mississippi, 2006-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Scope and Contents
    These correspondents include Chelius Carter, Mary Ann Connell, Jean Ann Jones, Frances Gresham, Mary R. Minor, Maxine Moore, and Kathleen McMillan Lane; the correspondence with the Reverend Bruce McMillan has been filed with his folder in clergy correspondence.
  - "Home to Holly Springs," covers and book jacket designs, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," editorial correspondence, 2005-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," editorial correspondence, 2007 January-August; 1 folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," editorial correspondence, 2007 September-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," first research trip, 2006 February-March; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," partial typescript draft with a note by Jan Karon “initial try at establishing dialect rules and standards”, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," page proofs, chapters 1-10, incomplete, 2007 August 14; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," page proofs, chapters 11-32, incomplete, 2007 August 14; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," paperback edition, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," publicity, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research general, 1998-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research general, 2006-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on diabetes and transplants, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on historic places of Holly Springs, including Rust College and the courthouse, 2005-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on kudzu and gardening, 1985, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on Memphis, Tennessee and the Natchez Trace, 2006-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on Southern small town humor, speech and culture, 2004-2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on the town of Holly Springs, Mississippi and the water tower, 2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research on trains, porters, and lines, 2007; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research trip travel arrangements with Sea Gate Travel Group, includes a photograph of Mrs. Pearl B. Richardson (1943), 1943, 2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," research trip travel arrangements with Sea Gate Travel Groups - Maps, 2005-2006; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," reviews and bestseller lists, 2007-2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," timeline for Father Tim and other characters, [2006]; 1 folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Home to Holly Springs," timeline for World War II, [2006] (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "In the Company of Others," author’s notes and drafts of scenes and dialogue, [2008-2010]; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "In the Company of Others," author’s notes and drafts of scenes and dialogue, [2008-2010]; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "In the Company of Others," author’s notes and drafts of scenes and dialogue with references to chapters, [2008-2010]; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "In the Company of Others," book jacket covers and publicity, 2010-2011; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "In the Company of Others," editorial correspondence, 2008-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "In the Company of Others," editorial correspondence, 2010 January-May; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "In the Company of Others," editorial correspondence, 2010 June-2012; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - emails concerning research questions, 2008-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - general (1 of 2 folders), 2003-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - general (2 of 2 folders), 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - Catholic Church and religious issues, 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - County Sligo, Ireland, and the surrounding areas, 2003-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - fishing in Ireland, 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - the Garda and legal issues, 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - Irish history and culture, including emigration to the United States, famine and slang, 2008-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes – Irish history and culture, including emigration to the United States, famine and slang, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - medicine and medical issues, 2008-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - medicine and medical issues, 2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - medicine and medical issues, undated; 1 folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - notebooks kept by Jan Karon, 2008; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - Timelines of Irish history and characters in the book, 2007-2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "In the Company of Others," research and notes - William Butler Yeats, 2008-2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "In This Mountain," editorial correspondence, 1998-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "In This Mountain," illustrations and covers, 2001-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "In This Mountain," typed manuscript drafts of chapters, including chapters 1, 2, 7, 8, and 9, [2000-2001?]; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "In This Mountain," typed manuscript, setting copy, chapters 1-5, [2002?]; 1 folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "In This Mountain," typed manuscript, setting copy, chapters 6-11, [2002?]; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "In This Mountain," typed manuscript, setting copy, chapters 12-17, [2002?]; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "In This Mountain," typed manuscript, setting copy, chapters 18-23, [2002?]; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "In This Mountain," page proofs, author's set, chapters 1-11, 2002 March 4; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "In This Mountain," page proofs, author's set, chapters 12-23, 2002 March 4; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "In This Mountain," promotional material, reviews, and bestseller lists, 2002-2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "In This Mountain," research and notes, 1996-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "In This Mountain," research and notes on diabetes, 1999-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," editorial correspondence, 1992-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," editorial correspondence, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," editorial correspondence, 2003; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," editorial correspondence, 2004-2006, 2010; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," illustrations and cover, 2002-2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," publicity, including reviews and magazine articles, bestseller lists, and fan response, such as "A Taste of Mitford", 2004-2005, 2009; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," recipes and research, including Jan Karon's "last meal" survey of friends, 1985-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," partial preliminary proof, pages 1-16, 2004 April 13; 1 folder(s) (Oversize box 1, Oversizefolder 1)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," recipes and text, 2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Jan Karon’s Mitford Cookbook and Kitchen Reader," recipes and text, 2003-2004; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "The Jan Karon Story Hour," featuring "The Tale of an Honest Bunny," "The Trellis and the Seed," and "Miss Fannie’s Hat" read by Jan Karon and her daughter, Candace Freeland, editorial correspondence, 2003-2005; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Jeremy The Tale of an Honest Bunny," editorial correspondence, 1997-2001; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Jeremy The Tale of an Honest Bunny," illustrations and cover, 1998; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Jeremy The Tale of an Honest Bunny," illustrations and cover, 1999-2002; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Jeremy The Tale of an Honest Bunny," manuscript, electrostatic copy, with a detailed editorial letter, March 23, 1997, from Elizabeth Law, 1988-1989, 1997; 1 folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 7)